jurgita.com 2007-12-14

# Privacy Policy

Author: jurgita.com  
Articles written: 363  
Source: [www.jurgita.com](http://www.jurgita.com/)  

---  
  
Article stats:  
Views: 10089   Votes: 0   Average: 0.00  
Added: 2005-07-29  Updated: 2007-01-08  

| 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

 _The Information We Collect:_

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on jurgita.com website. On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials and aditional information. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:  
Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Aditionally we collect following information from the models:  
Height  
Weigth  
Gender  
Birthday  
Bust  
Waist  
Hips  
Dress size  
Shoes size  
Information about hair, eyes, skin, teeth, ethnicity  
Profesional status  
Biography  
Experience  
Spoken languages  
Types of modeling

 _The Way We Use Information:_

Statistical information is gathered to present model to the clients. Exact stats are needed for the clients in order to know sizes of clothes, experience and statistical data of model to find proper assigments.  
Emails are not disclosed to public, internal messaging system is used to communicate.

 _Our Commitment To Data Security:_

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 _How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:_

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by www.jurgita.com by logging to your account and pressing update info button. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.  
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

 _How To Contact Us:_

By Email: Use the Form [Here](http://www.jurgita.com/tickets.php "Contact Us")  
By Phone: +370 37 451996  
By mail: Donelaicio 62-304, Kaunas, Lt-44248, Lithuania
